http://www.niagarasymphony.org/privacy-policy

Search
ConcertsMasterworks SeriesPops SeriesFamily SeriesTicketsSubscribeInformation & PricingSpecial OffersBox OfficeCustomer ServiceAbout NSOMusic DirectorOur HistoryCommunity Memories - 70 Years of the NSO Board & StaffJobsMusiciansGuest ArtistsAuditionsHire a MusicianLatest NewsConcert HallsPartridge HallThe Recital HallCommunity & EducationSummer Music CampSession 1 ProgrammingSession 2 ProgrammingThe AcademyDonors & SponsorsYouth ClubSpotlight On!NSO on the GONSO String QuartetNSO Arts & Minds Wind TrioConductor in the ClassroomInstrument Petting ZooTeacher ResourcesThe RecapStudy GuidesPaul van Dongen Memorial AwardSupport UsColleen Pohran Musicians Support CampaignBecome a DonorOvation 365Legacy CircleOur DonorsCorporate SponsorshipOur SponsorsCompassionate SymphonyAdvertiseEventsFace to Face and Fabulous! Wine RaffleVolunteer
Search
ConcertsTicketsAbout NSOCommunity & EducationSupport Us Buy Tickets
Join Our Mailing List
Latest News
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Watch & Listen
Privacy Policy
The Niagara Symphony Orchestra (NSO) respects your right to privacy and is committed to using your personal information in a respectful and useful way. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, address, telephone number, email address, and credit card information. The NSO does not sell, lend, or exchange any of this information.
All personal information submitted when purchasing tickets through the FirstOntario Performing Arts Centre box office is private and confidential. To authorize the Performing Arts Centre to release your information to the NSO, please indicate to the clerk that you consent to share your information with the NSO. If you also consent to receive email updates from the NSO, please indicate this information to the clerk.
ConcertsTicketsAbout NSOCommunity & EducationSupport Us
11 Bond St., Suite 207,
St. Catharines On L2R 4Z4
T: 905.687.4993
E: info@niagarasymphony.org
Charitable Registration #BN 11924 7328RR0001
ConcertsMasterworks SeriesPops SeriesFamily SeriesAbout NSOMusic DirectorOur HistoryBoard & StaffMusiciansConcert HallsLatest NewsCommunity & EducationSummer Music CampYouth ClubSpotlight On!NSO on the GOTeacher ResourcesSupport UsColleen Pohran Musicians Support CampaignBecome a DonorCorporate SponsorshipCompassionate SymphonyEventsAdvertiseVolunteerWine RaffleTicketsSubscribeInformation & PricingSpecial OffersBox OfficeCustomer Service
Privacy Policy 2020 © Niagara Symphony Orchestra
